Bardhi Grainca

Bardhi.grainca@hotmail.com - (389) 76-466-033 - Skopje, Macedonia - My Website

I'm a designer who codes. I am currently doing my MSc in Software Eng. In my free time I'm always searching for new challenges to conquer, because design and coding is my passion. I am a bit of a Jack – or Jill – of all design trades. Being well-versed allows me to maintain full aesthetic control when building brands – touching on everything from Information Architecture, UI/UX and mobile apps, to illustrating icons, graphics and logos. I also have 2 years of working experience in DevOps Infrastructures and my strong culture for enterprise DevOps teams has been engraved in my daily life and is part of me.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Singular Nov 2019 – April 2020

DevOps Engineer

Skopje

- Continuous integration (CI) continuous delivery (CD) with Jenkins
- Monitoring with Grafana (Percona), PRTG
- Troubleshooting application bugs
- Database management (MySQL)
- Log management (Graylog)
- Python Scripts, Bash Scripts

Stopanska Banka Main Branch

Jan 2019 - Nov 2019

System analyst

Skopje

- Collaborating with Business Analysts, Project Leads to resolve issues and ensuring solutions are viable
- Creating system guidelines and manuals for the organization
- Troubleshooting technical issues

SEAVUS Nov 2017 – Jan 2019

It and Operation Engineer

Skopje

- Diagnosing and solving customer software problems
- Provide technical assistance to the costumers like VOLVO, Rolls Royce, Ford, Tesla, and NATO.
- Test and reproduce reported issues and answer the technical questions, resolve customer problems.
- Provide assistance concerning the use of computer hardware and software, including operating systems and application, databases, network, security.

Web Design, Graphic design

Nov 2015 - Present

Freelancer

Skopje

- As a part-time freelancer I've worked on smaller and bigger projects.
- I have worked with Allran Electric, RealRok, Fahrenheit Mechanical NYC, SBNY Construction Company, on their corporate identity and web design/development.

EDUCATION

South East European University

2014 - 2017

Degree (BS), Majors (Computer Science)

Skopje

- Won 2 certificates on leadership and coding, also been part of NASA Space App Challenge
- I've won 1 place 2 years in a row in swimming competition

SKILLS & INTERESTS

- Skills: MySQL, SOAP, TOAD, LDAP, APACHE, .NET, SAP, Customer Service 1nd Level, 2nd Level;
- System Administrator, Windows Server 14, 16, Linux, VMware;
- Prototyping in XD, PSD, Al and converting them into Functional Web pages.
- HTML/CSS/Java Script, jQuery, UX/UI, Bootstrap, Python, Bash Scripting

Interests: Puns; Sleeping; Web-Design; Politics; Traveling;